gamesgofree.com 2014-02-12

# Privacy Policy - GamesGoFree.com - Download Full PC Games and Play for Free!

1\. Introduction

BoomeranGO, Inc. is the official proprietor of GamesGoFree.com . This privacy statement indicates the way we collect and use the personal information you provide on our website. GamesGoFree.com abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

2.Information we collect

Traditionally for the most websites, we gather information automatically and store it in log files. This information contains internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click-stream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual visitors, to analyze trends, to administer the website, to track visitors’ movements around the site and to gather information about the geographic location of our visitors as a whole.

GamesGoFree.com can collect personal information from you on a voluntary basis. This information may include personal information such as your name and e-mail address.

By allowing you to send e-mail to us, we are not attempting to collect any personal information about you. We will only use personal information (such as name and e-mail address) contained in your e-mail to respond to your specific inquiry or comments in the e-mail. Although we may retain your e-mail for a period of time, we will not use any personal information contained in your e-mail for any purpose other than responding to your specific inquiry or comments.

3\. Internet Safety

We take all necessary security arrangements to protect against unauthorized access to unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include domestic reviews of our data base, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. We strongly recommend that Parents take time to communicate and educate their children about Internet Safety.

4\. Cookies

A "cookie" is a small file that contains a line of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. However, we do not use cookies to store personal information such as your name. You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Thus, Google, as a third party supplier, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

5\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We retain the right to make changes in this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes in a conspicuous manner to this Privacy Policy.

6\. Contact Information

Please use our contact form if you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy.
